Open
this note again you are cheating Kareena hey
big papa in ludo game okay so I am always happy so this is the
ultimate what did you promise I had a dose still left hey friend she has started giving
orders like dada
all the cricket she has put on a mask for the first time
[music] it
is baba father's day I should have told you
that he has become my pet so that from the
establishment of all those processes now get used to it
now the log out is ending
no promise promise promise day is just like the clouds
who have always kept their promise of being with us for
safety in the same way you also keep doing your duty he is
like a father for baba